[{"answer": " It was pretty nice of Amanda to give us all of these clothes", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 12, "question": "", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " I know.  She said they were her old clothes that she didnt want anymore, bu", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 13, "question": " It was pretty nice of Amanda to give us all of these clothes", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " Well, you know Jennifer.  She has more clothes and shoes than anyone ", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 17, "question": " I know.  She said they were her old clothes that she didnt want anymore, bu", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Yeah, I think she wears a new outfit everyday", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Well, you know Jennifer.  She has more clothes and shoes than anyone ", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " All the better for us", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 22, "question": " Yeah, I think she wears a new outfit everyday", "qSentId": 21},{"answer": " OK, lets start looking through all of this stuff", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 23, "question": " All the better for us", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Lets do it", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 24, "question": " OK, lets start looking through all of this stuff", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Look at this skirt.  Thats cute.  It would look great on you, sis", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 25, "question": " Lets do it", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " What size is it", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 26, "question": " Look at this skirt.  Thats cute.  It would look great on you, sis", "qSentId": 25},{"answer": " Its a four", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 30, "question": " What size is it", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " A four?  I dont think I could squeeze into that.  Id have to diet for like si", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Its a four", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " Oh whatever.  What about this skirt", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 35, "question": " A four?  I dont think I could squeeze into that.  Id have to diet for like si", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " No way!  Its way too short.  Im not in my twenties anymore, you know", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 36, "question": " Oh whatever.  What about this skirt", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " OK, OK", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 37, "question": " No way!  Its way too short.  Im not in my twenties anymore, you know", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Oh, these are nice jeans.  Look, theyre designer  Calvin Klein", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 38, "question": " OK, OK", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Ooh, those are nice", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Oh, these are nice jeans.  Look, theyre designer  Calvin Klein", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Sorry, I saw them first.  Theyre mine", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 40, "question": " Ooh, those are nice", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " Thats OK.  Heres another pair.  These are Armani.  I get a pair too", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Sorry, I saw them first.  Theyre mine", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Armani is pricey.  How can our sister afford all of these nice clothes on ", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Thats OK.  Heres another pair.  These are Armani.  I get a pair too", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " Her husbands a lawyer, remember", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Armani is pricey.  How can our sister afford all of these nice clothes on ", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " Oh, yeah.  How could I forget?  She mentions it every time we see her", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 47, "question": " Her husbands a lawyer, remember", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " I know.  She likes to rub it in", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 48, "question": " Oh, yeah.  How could I forget?  She mentions it every time we see her", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " Look Mandy.  This dress is really cute.  Its a size four.  It would fit you", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 49, "question": " I know.  She likes to rub it in", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " That is cute.  Do you think that blue color would suit me", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 50, "question": " Look Mandy.  This dress is really cute.  Its a size four.  It would fit you", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " I think it would go great with your eyes", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 51, "question": " That is cute.  Do you think that blue color would suit me", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " Ill take it", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 52, "question": " I think it would go great with your eyes", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Here are some matching pumps that go with that dress.  Do you like these", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Ill take it", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " I think Amanda has bigger feet than me.  What size are they", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Here are some matching pumps that go with that dress.  Do you like these", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": "Nines", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 55, "question": " I think Amanda has bigger feet than me.  What size are they", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Oh, yeah.  Thats too big.  I wear seven and a halfs", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Nines", "qSentId": 55},{"answer": " Me too.  I guess we can give those to someone else", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 57, "question": " Oh, yeah.  Thats too big.  I wear seven and a halfs", "qSentId": 56},{"answer": " Here are some t-shirts.  What about these", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 61, "question": " Me too.  I guess we can give those to someone else", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " Those are soft.  I like the material.  How many are there", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Here are some t-shirts.  What about these", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " Eight", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Those are soft.  I like the material.  How many are there", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Want to take four each", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 64, "question": " Eight", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Sure.  Ill take the black and white ones, and you take the other colors.  Yo", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 65, "question": " Want to take four each", "qSentId": 64},{"answer": " True.  Ill take them", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Sure.  Ill take the black and white ones, and you take the other colors.  Yo", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " Wow!  Look at this.  A wool winter coat.  Feel how heavy it is", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 70, "question": " True.  Ill take them", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Wow!  Thats really nicely tailored.  That must have been expensive", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 71, "question": " Wow!  Look at this.  A wool winter coat.  Feel how heavy it is", "qSentId": 70},{"answer": " You want it", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Wow!  Thats really nicely tailored.  That must have been expensive", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " Nah.  I dont think Ill ever get a chance to wear that in Florida", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 73, "question": " You want it", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " I could wear it when I travel for business to Boston, dont you think", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 74, "question": " Nah.  I dont think Ill ever get a chance to wear that in Florida", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " Sure.  Why not", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 75, "question": " I could wear it when I travel for business to Boston, dont you think", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " I guess were not going to have to go shopping for a while now.  Look at all o", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 76, "question": " Sure.  Why not", "qSentId": 75},{"answer": "  I guess were lucky to have a rich and generous sister", "docId": "11-06", "aSentId": 80, "question": " I guess were not going to have to go shopping for a while now.  Look at all o", "qSentId": 79}]
